<?xml version='1.0' standalone='yes'?>
<tips>
  <tip>
    <day>01/01/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Start the New Year off right—resolve to lower your carbon footprint.  Do you know what yours is?  <a href="http://www.carbonfootprint.com/calculator.aspx" target="_blank">Online calculators make it easy</a>.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>01/02/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Recycle away your carbon footprint.  By recycling all of your home’s wasted newsprint, cardboard, glass, and metal, you can reduce carbon dioxide emissions by <a href="http://recycling.colorado.edu/education_and_outreach/recycling_facts.html" target="_blank">850 pounds</a> a year.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>01/03/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Change a light, change the world.  Switching to those funny looking compact fluorescent bulbs produces the same amount of light with <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Compact_fluorescent_lamp" target="_blank">the electricity</a>.  In addition, they last 8-15 times longer!]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>01/04/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Why are compact fluorescent bulbs so much more efficient?  The wow comes from the how.  Instead of using electricity to heat and light up a filament, they use it to convert gas into UV light, which requires <a href="http://www.thebulb.com/store/t-savingscalculator.aspx" target="_blank">75% less electricity</a>.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>01/05/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Wintertime <a href="http://www.residential-landscape-lighting-design.com/energy_benefits_ceiling_fans.htm" target="_blank">Fan Plan</a>:  in the winter, run your ceiling fan in a clockwise direction to push warm air to the ceiling.  You can lower your heating bills by 10%.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>01/06/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.epa.gov/waste/hazard/wastetypes/universal/lamps/live.htm" target="_blank">Remember to recycle your compact fluorescent bulbs</a>.  CFL bulbs last up to 10 times longer than normal bulbs, but they contain mercury; so when they do run out, recycle them to prevent the mercury from ending up in a landfill.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>01/07/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[You CAN earn your couch potato time!  One recycled aluminum can saves enough electricity to operate a TV for <a href="http://earth911.com/reduce/energy-costs-and-conservation-facts/" target="_blank">three hours</a>.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>01/08/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Run a tight ship!  Loose-fitting windows can lose up to five times more heat than windows with a normal fit.  <a href="http://www.energysavers.gov/your_home/insulation_airsealing/index.cfm/mytopic=11280" target="_blank">Weather strip your windows</a>.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>01/09/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[If your showerhead was made before 1992, you might <a href="http://electrical.hardwarestore.com/learning/8-simple-steps-to-saving-energy.aspx" target="_blank">benefit from a low-flow showerhead</a>. Quality, low-flow fixtures cost about $10 to $20 a piece and can help you reduce water expenses by 25%–60%.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>01/10/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Take the <a href="http://www.energysavers.gov/your_home/water_heating/index.cfm/mytopic=13050" target="_blank">low-flow showerhead test</a>: place a bucket in the shower and time how long it takes to fill to 1-gallon.  If it takes less than 20 seconds, you are sending too much water and money down the drain.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>01/11/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Make a greener tomorrow with yesterday’s news.  Every day, Americans buy about <a href="http://www.uoregon.edu/~recycle/TRIVIA.htm" target="_blank">62 million newspapers</a> and throw out around 44 million of them.  If we recycled just half of our newsprint every year, we could take 3,200 garbage trucks off the road.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>01/12/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Don’t toss that pop can in the trash—recycle it.  To make a ton of aluminum from <a href="http://www.uoregon.edu/~recycle/TRIVIA.htm" target="_blank">raw materials</a>, we have to treat and dispose of 3,290 lbs. of red mud, 2,900 lbs. of carbon dioxide, 81 lbs. of air pollutants and 789 lbs. of solid wastes.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>01/13/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[If you are going to be out of a room for more than five minutes, shut off the light.  Using compact fluorescent bulbs?  The rule of thumb is to turn them off if you’ll be away for <a href="http://www.energysavers.gov/your_home/lighting_daylighting/index.cfm/mytopic=12280" target="_blank">15 minutes or longer</a>.   ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>01/14/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Should you turn your computer off or not?  The <a href="http://www.energysavers.gov/your_home/appliances/index.cfm/mytopic=10070" target="_blank">rule of thumb</a> is to turn monitors off for periods over 20 minutes and turn off the CPU if you’ll be away more than two hours.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>01/15/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Do you recycle your motor oil?  About 62% of all oil-related pollution in the U.S. is caused by improper disposal of used motor oil.  It’s the single largest source of oil pollution (over 40%) in our nation’s waterways.  <a href="http://earth911.com/" target="_blank">Click here to find a recycling center near you</a>. ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>01/16/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[If you have a fireplace, <a href="http://www.energyquest.ca.gov/saving_energy/index.html" target="_blank">close the damper</a> when you don’t have a fire burning.  An open fireplace damper can let 8% of heat from your furnace escape through the chimney!  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>01/17/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Save energy and money by using less hot water.  One easy option?  Prevent leaks.  A leak of one drip per second can cost <a href="http://www.energysavers.gov/your_home/water_heating/index.cfm/mytopic=13050" target="_blank">$1 per month</a>.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>01/18/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Hot tip!  For cooking and baking small quantities, use an electric skillet, broiler oven, or toaster oven.  They use half the energy of an oven.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>01/19/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://electrical.hardwarestore.com/learning/8-simple-steps-to-saving-energy.aspx" target="_blank">Get in the mood for dimmer switches</a>.  Change the mood of a room and your energy bill by dimming or brightening the lights with a dimmer switch.  Dimming the light by just 10 percent more than doubles the bulb life.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>01/20/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Want to <a href="http://www.energysavers.gov/your_home/water_heating/index.cfm/mytopic=13090" target="_blank">reduce your water heating costs</a>?  Lower the thermostat setting on your water heater.  Each 10ºF reduction in water temperature saves 3%–5% in energy costs.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>01/21/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Green up your living space with a <a href="http://www.energysavers.gov/your_home/energy_audits/index.cfm/mytopic=11170" target="_blank">home energy audit</a>.  You’ll be amazed how you can save.  Call your utility company to see if they have a free audit service or go to <a href="http://www.energysavers.gov" target="_blank">www.energysavers.gov</a> to learn how to do it yourself.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>01/22/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Don’t let your hot water pipes get cold—<a href="http://www.energysavers.gov/your_home/water_heating/index.cfm/mytopic=13070" target="_blank">insulate your hot water heater</a>!  You’ll reduce heat loss, raise temperature 2º–4ºF and save time and water by wasting less time waiting for it to get hot.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>01/23/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Low is the way to go.  About <a href="http://www.savethewater.org/water/Columns/WaterFact.asp?typeid=58&amp;parentid=2&amp;lid=2&amp;imaid=3&amp;videos=&amp;id=57" target="_blank">75%</a> of the water we use in our homes is used in the bathroom.  Unless you have a low flush toilet, you use about five to seven gallons of water with every flush!  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>01/24/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Be sure to always <a href="http://www.appropedia.org/Washing_and_drying_clothes" target="_blank">wash and dry full loads</a>.  If you have to wash a small load, make sure to change the water-level setting.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>01/25/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[On again, off again!  Leaving the tap on while you are brushing your teeth can send more than <a href="http://www.savethewater.org/water/Columns/WaterFact.asp?typeid=58&amp;parentid=2&amp;lid=2&amp;imaid=3&amp;videos=&amp;id=57" target="_blank">five gallons</a> of water down the drain.  Try turning the water on and off when you are brushing your teeth, it uses only ½ gallon!  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>01/26/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Don’t heat the neighborhood!  <a href="http://www.energysavers.gov/your_home/insulation_airsealing/index.cfm/mytopic=11260" target="_blank">Caulking and weather stripping</a>—two simple <a href="http://www.energysavers.gov/your_home/insulation_airsealing/index.cfm/mytopic=11230" target="_blank">air sealing</a> techniques—will pay for themselves in energy savings within one year.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>01/27/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Just say no to ironing!  You can save loads of energy and time, and still look good.  Just 5-10 minutes in the dryer will remove the wrinkles on most shirts and pants…let them finish drying on hangers.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>01/28/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Read electronically and feed the world.  Tropical rain forests, which are home to about half of all the Earth’s plant and animal species, are being destroyed at the rate of <a href="http://www.rain-tree.com/facts.htm" target="_blank">100 acres per minute</a>.  The more you read online, the more you help.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>01/29/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Think before you toss.  Of the garbage Americans throw out, half could be recycled.  That’s enough to fill a <a href="http://www.uoregon.edu/~recycle/TRIVIA.htm" target="_blank">football stadium</a> from top to bottom every day.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>01/30/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Take a second to cut your computer’s energy consumption by 80%, forever.  Just enable the energy efficiency settings in the control panel under “power options” (usually labeled “sleep”, “hibernate” or “standby” mode).]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>01/31/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Recycling glass has clear benefits.  A ton of glass produced from raw materials creates 384 <a href="http://www.green-networld.com/tips/glass.htm" target="_blank">pounds of mining waste</a>, using 50% recycled glass cuts it by about 75%.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>02/01/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Do you wash dishes with the tap running?  Try filling the basin instead; you’ll save about <a href="http://www.savethewater.org/water/Columns/WaterFact.asp?typeid=58&amp;parentid=2&amp;lid=2&amp;imaid=3&amp;videos=&amp;id=57" target="_blank">25 gallons</a> of water every time you do the dishes.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>02/02/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[If you think the economic and environmental cost of bottled water is justified by how much “healthier” it is, think again.  Federal standards are higher for tap water than they are for bottled water.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>02/03/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Is your toilet running?  Better catch it!  Leaks are costly.  <a href="http://www.oberlin.edu/recycle/facts.html" target="_blank">A leaky toilet can waste more than 100 gallons of water every single day</a>!]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>02/04/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Recycle One Get One Free.  Recycled glass can be made with <a href="http://earth911.com/reduce/energy-costs-and-conservation-facts" target="_blank">50 percent</a> less energy than virgin glass.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>02/05/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Even small leaks are costly.  A faucet that leaks enough water to fill a soda bottle every 30 minutes will waste <a href="http://www.energyquest.ca.gov/saving_energy/index.html" target="_blank">2,192 gallons</a> of water a year.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>02/06/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Take shorter showers!  You won’t just save water; you’ll save a lot of energy too.  <a href="http://www.seastudios.org/climate-friendly_checklist.pdf" target="_blank">Water heaters account for nearly ¼ of your home’s energy use</a>.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>02/07/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.appropedia.org/Washing_and_drying_clothes" target="_blank">Inspect your dryer vent</a> regularly to make sure it is not blocked.  It will save energy and could just prevent a fire.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>02/08/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Eat local.  From field to fork, an average dinner travels more than <a href="http://www.eatlocal.net/why.html" target="_blank">1,500 miles</a>.  Locally grown foods are a fresher, more sustainable choice that benefits your community too!  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>02/09/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Make pasta tonight!  Did you know it takes <a href="http://www.savethewater.org/water/Columns/WaterFact.asp?typeid=58&amp;parentid=2&amp;lid=2&amp;imaid=3&amp;videos=&amp;id=57" target="_blank">100 times</a> more water to produce a pound of meat than a pound of wheat?  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>02/10/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Grandmother knows best; draft snakes are cheap, easy and green.  Whether you buy a draft snake at a hardware store or <a href="http://www.thedailygreen.com/green-homes/latest/door-draft-stoppers-draft-snakes-460109" target="_blank">make your own</a>, <a href="http://www.thedailygreen.com/going-green/tips/draft-stoppers-door-snakes" target="_blank">reducing drafts can cut down energy bills 5-30%</a>.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>02/11/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Beware of dry cleaners claiming to be <a href="http://www.livescience.com/health/070130_bad_drycleaning.html" target="_blank">organic</a>!  The term organic means something very different when it describes chemicals.  Scientifically, gasoline is organic, because it has a chain of carbon in it—but that doesn’t mean you want to wash your clothes in it!    ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>02/12/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Wash in cold water!  When you wash clothes, 95% of the energy goes to heating the water.  Unless you have an oily stain, your clothes will come perfectly clean in cold water and you can cut your cost per load from <a href="http://michaelbluejay.com/electricity/laundry.html" target="_blank">58¢ to 3¢</a>.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>02/13/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Dry towels and heavier cottons in a <a href="http://www.appropedia.org/Washing_and_drying_clothes" target="_blank">separate load</a> from lighter-weight clothes.  Be sure not to over-dry your clothes.  If your machine has a moisture sensor, use it, you will save money.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>02/14/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Be my funny (green) valentine!  Send an amusing <a href="http://www.care2.com/send/catvalentine1.html" target="_blank">e-card while saving the world</a>, give <a href="http://www.care2.com/greenliving/easy-greening-chocolate.html" target="_blank">fair trade chocolates</a>, make a home-cooked meal using locally grown food or <a href="http://dinegreen.com/customers/default.asp" target="_blank">locate a certified green restaurant</a> near you.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>02/15/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Buy recycled paper.  Every ton of recycled paper keeps almost <a href="http://www.uoregon.edu/~recycle/TRIVIA.htm" target="_blank">60 pounds</a> of pollutants out of the atmosphere that would have been produced had the paper had been manufactured using virgin resources.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>02/16/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Hot is not cool.  If you washed your clothes in hot water instead of cold, in a year you would use more electricity than if you left the refrigerator door open <a href="http://michaelbluejay.com/electricity/cooling.html" target="_blank">24 hours a day</a>.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>02/17/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Changing the setting on your wash cycle from hot to cold saves big bucks.  It also saves your clothes.  Hot water shrinks fabrics, fades colors and wears your clothes out quicker.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>02/18/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Set it and forget it!  Change the setting on your printer to print on both sides of the paper.  Without ever having to think about it again, you’ll save lots of trees and ink!]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>02/19/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.chow.com/stories/10870" target="_blank">Rethink your take out habit</a>.  Takeout food uses containers and plastic that are usually non-recyclable.  Non-degradable plastic doesn’t begin to decompose in a landfill for at least 1,000 years.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>02/20/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[If you have an oily stain that requires warm water, just use a warm pre-soak.  Soaking clothes in warm water is usually just as good or better as hot water with no soak.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>02/21/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Recycle those cans!  Every three months, Americans throw away enough aluminum cans to rebuild our <a href="http://earth911.com/reduce/energy-costs-and-conservation-facts/" target="_blank">entire commercial air fleet</a>!  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>02/22/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Landscaping can actually reduce your heating and cooling costs.  On average, <a href="http://www.energysavers.gov/your_home/landscaping/index.cfm/mytopic=11910" target="_blank">landscaping for energy efficiency</a> provides enough savings to return an initial investment in less than eight years.  Now is a good time to plan spring projects.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>02/23/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Here’s a glass cut that won’t hurt:  recycled glass generates <a href="http://earth911.com/reduce/energy-costs-and-conservation-facts/" target="_blank">20% less air pollution</a> and 50% less water pollution.  One ton of glass made from 50 percent recycled materials saves <a href="http://earth911.com/reduce/energy-costs-and-conservation-facts/" target="_blank">250 pounds</a> of mining waste.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>02/24/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Thinking about getting a new cell phone?  You can save the earth and help our troops by donating your old cell phone to <a href="http://www.cellphonesforsoldiers.com/" target="_blank">www.cellphonesforsoldiers.com</a>.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>02/25/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.appropedia.org/Washing_and_drying_clothes" target="_blank">Clean the lint filter</a> in the dryer after every load.  You will improve air circulation and dry your clothes faster.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>02/26/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Do you shut your computer off at night when you leave the office?  If everyone did, we could get by with eight less large power stations in the U.S. alone.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>02/27/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Run around the house naked.  You’ll have fewer clothes to wash!]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>02/28/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Drips can be a drain!  The smallest drip from a leaky faucet can waste over <a href="http://www.savethewater.org/water/Columns/WaterFact.asp?typeid=58&amp;parentid=2&amp;lid=2&amp;imaid=3&amp;videos=&amp;id=57" target="_blank">50 gallons</a> of water every single day.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>02/29/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Drips can be a drain!  The smallest drip from a leaky faucet can waste over <a href="http://www.savethewater.org/water/Columns/WaterFact.asp?typeid=58&amp;parentid=2&amp;lid=2&amp;imaid=3&amp;videos=&amp;id=57" target="_blank">50 gallons</a> of water every single day.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/01/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Sign up for renewable energy!  Most utility providers offer a renewable energy or green power program.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/02/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[More is less.  For each pound of aluminum you recycle, you eliminate the need to strip mine <a href="http://earth911.com/reduce/energy-costs-and-conservation-facts/" target="_blank">four pounds</a> of bauxite ore.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/03/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Why do they call the Amazon Rainforest the "Lungs of our Planet"?  Because more than <a href="http://www.rain-tree.com/facts.htm" target="_blank">20%</a> of the world’s oxygen is produced in the Amazon Rainforest.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/04/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Bright idea:  go fluorescent!  Replacing just one 50-watt light bulb with an 11-watt compact fluorescent bulb saves more than 685 pounds of CO2 per year!  Over the life of the bulb, you’ll also save <a href="http://www.thebulb.com/store/t-savingscalculator.aspx" target="_blank">$30 or more in energy costs</a>.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/05/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[If every US household replaced six 60-watt incandescent light bulbs with 13-watt compact fluorescent light bulbs, it would be equivalent to taking <a href="http://www.thebulb.com/store/t-savingscalculator.aspx" target="_blank">3,188,894 cars</a> off the road - for good.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/06/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Red Bull isn’t the only way to get energy from a can.  Recycling cans to produce new ones enables the production of up to <a href="http://environment.about.com/od/globalwarming/tp/globalwarmtips.htm" target="_blank">20 times more</a> cans for the same amount of energy.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/07/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Send your aluminum can to be recycled and you could be drinking from it again in as little as <a href="http://www.cancentral.com/funFacts.cfm" target="_blank">60 days</a>.  That’s how long it takes to return it to the grocer’s shelf as a new, filled can after collection, re-melting, rolling, manufacturing and distribution.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/08/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Early spring is a good time to plant a tree.  A single tree can absorb one ton of carbon dioxide over its lifetime.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/09/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Can you believe it?  Every three seconds a baby is born.  In that time, <a href="http://www.cancentral.com/funFacts.cfm" target="_blank">140 cans</a> are born.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/10/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Are you an Energy Star?  Get credit for it with an <a href="http://www.energystar.gov/index.cfm?c=bldrs_lenders_raters.energy_efficient_mortgage" target="_blank">Energy Efficient Mortgage</a>.   EEMs are conventional, FHA and VA mortgages that give credit for energy efficiency.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/11/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Leave the shoes at the door!  No need to pollute your home with oil, antifreeze, animal waste, particulate pollution, pollen and other toxins you pick up on your shoes.  Less dirt tracked in means less work, water, energy, and fewer chemicals too!  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/12/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Eat up those leftovers.  Americans throw away about <a href="http://www.bringrecycling.org/benefits.html" target="_blank">10% of the food</a> they buy at the grocery store.  This dumps the equivalent of more than 21 million shopping bags of food into landfills every year.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/13/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Want to hang laundry outdoors but your city or homeowners association has rules against it?  The pro-line drying movement, headed up by <a href="http://www.laundrylist.org/advocacy/76-the-right-to-dry-campaign" target="_blank">Right to Dry</a>, offers good resources for securing your right to solar drying.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/14/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Get audited!  Many utility providers offer energy audits to help you identify ways to save energy and money.  If they don’t offer this service, ask them to help you find a professional (it should cost between $50-200).  Or, <a href="http://www.eere.energy.gov/" target="_blank">do your own energy audit</a>.   ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/15/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[When it comes to glass, the advantages of recycling are clear.  Using recycled glass to make new glass cuts related air pollution by <a href="http://ssi.ucsd.edu/esiportal/index.php?option=com_content&amp;task=view&amp;id=179&amp;Itemid=101" target="_blank">up to 20%</a>.   Recycling one ton of glass saves the equivalent in energy of <a href="http://www.recycling-revolution.com/recycling-facts.html" target="_blank">10 gallons of oil</a>.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/16/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Make it your job to recycle.  Recycling has created an estimated <a href="http://www.epa.gov/waste/conserve/rrr/rmd/rei-rw/pdf/factsheet_nat.pdf" target="_blank">1.1 million jobs</a> as well as an additional <a href="http://www.epa.gov/waste/conserve/rrr/rmd/rei-rw/pdf/factsheet_nat.pdf" target="_blank">1.4 million jobs</a> indirectly supported by the recycling and reuse industry.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/17/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Cover your pots when you boil water.  The water will heat faster and you’ll save energy]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/18/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Use cloth napkins!  Replacing paper napkins with cloth saves trees, and it’s nicer too]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/19/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://planetgreen.discovery.com/home-garden/laundry-liquid-soap-tip.html" target="_blank">Choose concentrated laundry detergent</a>.  Concentrated detergents save packaging, CO2 and money.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/20/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Wait to run your dishwasher with a full load.  You can save up to <a href="http://www.docstoc.com/docs/14968996/CARBON-DIOXIDE-REDUCTIONS" target="_blank">200 pounds of carbon dioxide</a> and $40 per year!  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/21/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.greenercars.org/drivingtips.htm" target="_blank">Don’t take it to the limit</a>!  Driving 75 mph instead of 65 mph will lower your fuel economy by about 10%, and can dramatically increase tailpipe pollution.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/22/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Recycle what you read!  We dump most of the magazines printed in the U.S. each year into landfills.  If we recycled just half of them, we could save over <a href="http://www.uoregon.edu/~recycle/TRIVIA.htm" target="_blank">12 million</a> cubic yards of landfill space.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/23/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Reign in paper waste on behalf of the rainforest.  Rainforests that once covered <a href="http://www.rain-tree.com/facts.htm" target="_blank">14%</a> of the Earth's land surface now cover less than 6%.  Experts estimate that the last remaining rainforests could be consumed within just 40 years.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/24/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Start a compost pile.  <a href="http://www.epa.gov/airtoxics/burn/burnalt1.pdf" target="_blank">Composting</a> does more to reduce our landfill burden.  Fallen leaves contain 50-80% of the nutrients that a tree extracts from the Earth.  By composting them, we’re helping the earth replenish itself.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/25/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Composting offers rich rewards.  Recycling an average-size family’s yard waste can make about <a href="http://www.uoregon.edu/~recycle/TRIVIA.htm" target="_blank">300-400 pounds</a> of finished compost, or humus, a year.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/26/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Composting?  Be sure to use red worms.  They can consume <a href="http://whatcom.wsu.edu/ag/compost/redwormsedit.htm" target="_blank">½ pound</a> of food waste every single day.  How many do you need?  Figure on a worm to daily food ratio of 2:1]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/27/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Bag bagging!  <a href="http://www.ehow.com/how_3541_begin-compost-pile.html" target="_blank">Start composting</a> or <a href="http://www.ehow.com/how_2292947_make-mulch.html" target="_blank">mulching</a> leaves and grass clippings instead.  It’s easier than bagging, better for the planet and better for your lawn and garden’s health.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/28/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Now is a good time to plant landscaping that will shade your air conditioner condensing unit.  You could <a href="http://michaelbluejay.com/electricity/cooling.html" target="_blank">save up to 10%</a> in electricity costs.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/29/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[We need to change the way we change our oil.  A quart of used motor oil can pollute 250,000 gallons of water and one acre of land one inch deep.   Americans throw away enough used motor oil every year to fill 120 supertankers.  <a href="http://earth911.com/" target="_blank">Click here to find a motor oil recycling center near you</a>. ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/30/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[More than <a href="http://www.bringrecycling.org/benefits.html" target="_blank">⅔ of the material</a> in landfills is degradable.  But it doesn’t break down because landfills are kept dry to help prevent contamination from runoff.  Newspapers are still readable after 20 years.  Some foods—like T-bone steaks and hot dogs—don’t break down for more than 10 years.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>03/31/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Check your oven timer instead of opening the door, your food will cook faster without letting heat and energy escape.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>04/01/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[April is National Volunteer Month.  This year, consider a volunteer vacation.  Many volunteer vacation options allow you to choose your cause, organization and location.  Check out <a href="http://www.charityguide.org/volunteer/vacations.htm" target="_blank">Charity Guide</a>, <a href="http://www.habitat.org/newsroom/2003archive/insitedoc005043.aspx" target="_blank">Habitat for Humanity</a>, and <a href="http://www.earthwatch.org/expedition" target="_blank">Earth Watch</a>.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>04/02/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Do your part to lower our dependence on foreign oil—recycle your motor oil.  If all used motor oil in the U.S. were recycled, it would result in a saving of 1.3 million barrels of oil per day.  <a href="http://earth911.com/" target="_blank">Find a recycling center near you</a>. ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>04/03/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[What kind of paper does your office use?  Recycled paper saves <a href="http://earth911.com/reduce/energy-costs-and-conservation-facts/" target="_blank">60%</a> on energy over virgin paper and generates 95% less air pollution.  Each ton of paper made from recycled materials saves 60 pounds of air pollution, <a href="http://earth911.com/reduce/energy-costs-and-conservation-facts/" target="_blank">17 trees and 7,000 gallons</a> of water.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>04/04/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Photocopy on both sides.  If offices throughout the country increased the rate of two-sided photocopying from the 1991 figure of 20 percent to 60 percent, they could save the equivalent of about <a href="http://earth911.com/reduce/energy-costs-and-conservation-facts/" target="_blank">15 million trees</a>.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>04/05/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Do you let the faucet run while you’re shaving?  You’re using <a href="http://www.savethewater.org/water/Columns/WaterFact.asp?typeid=58&amp;parentid=2&amp;lid=2&amp;imaid=3&amp;videos=&amp;id=57" target="_blank">15-20 gallons</a> of water each time.  Try filling the basin.  It uses only one gallon of water—saving up to 19 gallons with every shave!]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>04/06/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Buy less packaging.  <a href="http://recycling.colorado.edu/education_and_outreach/recycling_facts.html" target="_blank">Packaging is ⅓ of our waste</a> and accounts for one out of every 10 dollars we spend at the store.  Buy concentrated or in bulk, avoid single-servings and carry reusable cloth bags.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>04/07/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Recycle that cardboard box.  Americans use about 30 billion cardboard boxes a year.  If we recycled just one box a month, more than a <a href="http://www.uoregon.edu/~recycle/TRIVIA.htm" target="_blank">billion boxes</a> a year could be kept out of landfills.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>04/08/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Recycle those old phone books.  If Americans recycled every phone book each year, an estimated <a href="http://www3.niu.edu/recycling/alum_facts/page5.html" target="_blank">650,000 tons</a> of paper could be saved.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>04/09/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Recycling news:  an average family of three produces about <a href="http://www.uoregon.edu/~recycle/TRIVIA.htm" target="_blank">five pounds a week</a> or 250 pounds a year of used newspaper.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>04/10/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Toss it in the recycle bin instead of the trash.  Every year, enough paper is thrown away to make a <a href="http://earth911.com/reduce/energy-costs-and-conservation-facts/" target="_blank">12-foot wall</a> from New York to California.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>04/11/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Plant a tree.  One tree can filter up to <a href="http://www.thegreenteam.org/GT_SlashTrashColor.pdf" target="_blank">60 pounds of pollutants</a> from the air each year.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>04/12/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Want to save money and the planet by breaking your bottled water habit, but don’t like the taste of tap?  Install a water filter on your faucet.  <a href="http://www.waterfiltercomparisons.com/water_filter_comparison.php" target="_blank">Check out how different brands perform here</a> before you buy.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>04/13/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Beware of “<a href="http://www.eereblogs.energy.gov/energysavers/post/Stop-Paying-for-Energy-You-Arent-Using.aspx" target="_blank">energy vampires</a>”!  The average home has 40 products constantly plugged in and drawing power.  Unplug small charges and use power strips to turn off groups of products (like computer equipment).  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>04/14/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Every degree you lower your thermostat <a href="http://www.energysavers.gov/your_home/space_heating_cooling/index.cfm/mytopic=12720" target="_blank">saves you 1%</a> on your heating bill when the setback period is eight hours long.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>04/15/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Try to toss into the recycling bin three times as often as the trash.  About 80% of what Americans throw away is recyclable, yet our recycling rate is just <a href="http://www.wsaemc.org/Recycling/recycling%20Facts.htm" target="_blank">28%</a>.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>04/16/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[How about a trash diet?!  In a lifetime, the average American throws out 600 times his or her adult weight in trash.  That’s <a href="http://recycling.colorado.edu/education_and_outreach/recycling_facts.html" target="_blank">90,000 pounds</a> of garbage.  Toss less and lighten your load.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>04/17/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Set a personal goal to be below average.  If you’re an average American, it’s going to take <a href="http://www.funtrivia.com/askft/Question69386.html" target="_blank">465 trees</a> to provide you with a lifetime of paper.  Cutting your paper consumption by just one-third will save 150 trees!]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>04/18/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Styrofoam belongs in the recycle bin!  If you lined up all the polystyrene <a href="http://www3.niu.edu/recycling/alum_facts/page5.html" target="_blank">foam cups</a> made in just one day, they would circle the earth.  Polystyrene foam is not biodegradable, so it is a real problem in a landfill, but it IS recyclable.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>04/19/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Chose recycled paper with the most “post-consumer” content.  Paper from recycled materials results in 74% less air pollution and <a href="http://www.uoregon.edu/~recycle/TRIVIA.htm" target="_blank">35% less water pollution</a>.  Because recycled paper means any percentage is recycled, look for how much “post-consumer" content it has (e.g.  from recycling centers).  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>04/20/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Avoid plastic packaging whenever you can.  Plastic does not biodegrade.  Every American uses almost <a href="http://www.bringrecycling.org/benefits.html" target="_blank">200 pounds of plastic</a> in a year—and 30%, or 60 pounds of it, is packaging.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>04/21/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Put plastics in the recycling bin not the trash.  When buried, some plastic materials may last for <a href="http://www.bringrecycling.org/benefits.html" target="_blank">700 years</a>.  If the Pilgrims had six-packs, we’d still have the plastic rings from them today.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>04/22/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Happy Earth Day!  Make everyday Earth Day by making a resolution to take at least one positive green action each and every day. ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>04/23/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Make room for recycling.  Paper and cardboard make up <a href="http://www.alarecycling.com/facts.html" target="_blank">73%</a> of our landfills.  We tend to throw it away because the recycling bin is not as conveniently located.  Put a recycling box next to your trash and see how much more you recycle.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>04/24/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Make a ton of difference by recycling all of the paper you use.  Every ton of <a href="http://www.bringrecycling.org/benefits.html" target="_blank">recycled paper saves</a> approximately four barrels of oil, 4200-kilowatt hours of energy and enough energy to heat and air-condition the average North American home for at least six months.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>04/25/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Think of recycling as “re-gifting” the environment.  One ton of paper made completely from recycled scrap saves <a href="http://www.oberlin.edu/recycle/facts.html" target="_blank">7,000 gallons</a> of water, 4100-kilowatt hours of energy, three cubic yards of landfill space and 17 trees.   So when you recycle, you aren’t just eliminating waste, you are giving precious resources back to the earth.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>04/26/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Sacrifice your virginity!  Making a ton of virgin paper <a href"http://www.alarecycling.com/facts.html" target="_blank">requires 3,688 lbs.</a>  of wood, 24,000 gallons of water, 216 lbs.  of lime, 360 lbs.  of salt cake and 76 lbs.  of soda ash.  We then have to treat and dispose of 84 lbs.  of air pollutants, 36 lbs.  of water pollutants and 176 lbs.  of solid waste.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>04/27/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Weigh your options to eliminate waste.  Each of us generates on average <a href="http://recycling.colorado.edu/education_and_outreach/recycling_facts.html" target="_blank">4.4 pounds</a> of waste per day per person.  Cut back by just 25% and you can personally eliminate more than 400 pounds of waste in just one year.   ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>04/28/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Don’t buy into the myth of virgin paper.  Recycled paper is <a href="http://ecocrumbs.com/2009/03/recycled-office-products-paper-part-i/" target="_blank">more opaque, dense, and flexible</a> than paper made from virgin materials; it’s better for the earth and better for you.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>04/29/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Make a job out of recycling.  For every 15,000 tons of old newspaper recycled annually, <a href="http://www3.niu.edu/recycling/alum_facts/page5.html" target="_blank">30 jobs</a> are created to collect the paper, 40 jobs are created to process the paper, and 75 jobs are required to manufacture the newsprint.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>04/30/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Print not.  Waste not.  Americans discard <a href="http://www.bringrecycling.org/benefits.html" target="_blank">four million tons</a> of office paper every year, enough to build a 12 foot-high wall from New York to California.  Two easy solutions:  add a “please consider the environment before printing” signature to your email and put a paper recycling bin next to the trash can.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/01/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Put a cap on your bottle habits.  Americans use <a href="http://www3.niu.edu/recycling/alum_facts/page5.html" target="_blank">four million</a> plastic bottles every hour, yet only one bottle out of four is recycled.  If we recycled every plastic bottle we used, we would keep two billion tons of plastic out of landfills ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/02/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Rainy springs are a great time to start collecting rainwater for watering plants.  It’s an easy way to cut down on water usage and plants love it because rainwater is chemical-free, highly oxygenated and has a neutral PH.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/03/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Shrink your shrink-wrap footprint.  America makes enough low-density polyethylene (LDPE) plastic every year to shrink-wrap the state of Texas.  Most of it ends up in landfills.  <a href="http://www.ehow.com/how_5103711_recycle-shrink-wrap.html" target="_blank">Learn how you can recycle plastic wrap</a>.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/04/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Drink milk—you can build strong bones and park benches.  A six-foot plastic park bench can be built <a href="http://www.bringrecycling.org/benefits.html" target="_blank">with 1,050 recycled milk jugs</a>.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/05/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Recycle every can you can.  Americans use <a href="http://www.uoregon.edu/~recycle/TRIVIA.htm" target="_blank">100 million tin</a> and steel cans every day.  Make it a point to put all your cans in the recycling bin—not just drink cans.  Food cans, deodorant sprays, hairsprays, cleaning and polishing sprays all add up!  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/06/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Make a tin bin.  Americans throw away enough steel every year to <a href="http://www.bringrecycling.org/benefits.html" target="_blank">build all the new cars</a> made in America.  To make tin recycling easier and more top of mind, add a can container to your recycling system.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/07/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Get energized about tin recycling.  Making tin cans from recycled steel takes only <a href="http://www.oberlin.edu/recycle/facts.html" target="_blank">¼</a> of the energy needed to make them from new steel and cut water and air pollution by 75%.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/08/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Searching for a new way to go green?  Search on <a href="http://blackle.com/" target="_blank">Blackle</a> instead of Google.  Blackle is a search engine powered by Google with a black background instead of white, saving big on greenhouse gases.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/09/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[When you buy new tires, make sure the tire shop recycles your old ones.  <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tire_recycling" target="_blank">Americans discard more than 290 million tires a year</a>.  Eight of every ten tires wind up in landfills or “stockpiles.”  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/10/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Recycled tires offer real mileage.  Recycled tires have many uses from basketball courts to shoe products to playground material.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/11/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Give old tires new uses.  Use them for boat bumpers, make a sand box, a hanging table, a <a href="http://www.ehow.com/how_2085185_tire-swing.html" target="_blank">tire swing</a> or <a href="http://www.thegreenestdollar.com/2009/03/how-to-recycle-tires-in-your-garden/" target="_blank">garden planter</a>.  You can even <a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iIEpRE34EY8" target="_blank">make sandals out of old tires</a>!  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/12/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[The average baby generates <a href="http://www.thediaperhyena.com/diaper_drama_scene4_environment.htm" target="_blank">a ton of garbage</a> every year they’re in diapers!  Using cloth diapers and washing them at home isn’t the easiest choice to make, but it certainly is the greenest.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/13/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Help the planet, and your budget, by switching to cloth diapers.  Not only will you feel better about not adding to our nation’s landfill burden, you will feel good watching <a href="http://www.diaperpin.com/calculator/calculator.asp" target="_blank">the savings add up</a>!]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/14/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Tune up your neighborhood’s recycling habits—organize a drop off box for used motor oil.  One gallon of used oil can produce the same amount of motor oil as 42 gallons of crude oil while requiring about ⅓ of the energy.  <a href="http://earth911.com/" target="_blank">Dispose of the oil at a recycling center near you</a>. ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/15/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Try not to do your fair share.  Americans represent only 5% of the world’s population, but we generate <a href="http://www.bringrecycling.org/benefits.html" target="_balnk">30%</a> of the world’s garbage.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/16/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Weigh your options before you throw it out.  Can it be recycled?  Donated?  Reused?  In a lifetime, the average American throws away <a href="http://www.oberlin.edu/recycle/facts.html" target="_blank">600 times</a> his or her adult weight in garbage.  Adding it up, a 150-pound adult will leave a legacy of 90,000 pounds of trash for his or her children.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/17/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Cutting back on fast food cuts calories and trash.  Did you know that every $1,000 of fast food sales creates <a href="http://www.bringrecycling.org/benefits.html" target="_blank">200 pounds</a> of trash?]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/18/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Don’t throw away aluminum cans—recycle them!  It takes aluminum cans <a href="http://climate.weather.com/articles/dclandfill2009.html?page=5" target="_blank">80-200 years</a> to decompose in a landfill.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/19/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Don’t throw away glass—recycle it!  It takes glass <a href="http://climate.weather.com/articles/dclandfill2009.html?page=2" target="_blank">1,000,000 years</a> to decompose in a landfill]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/20/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Don’t throw away plastic—recycle it!  It takes plastic <a href="http://climate.weather.com/articles/dclandfill2009.html?page=2" target="_blank">500-1000 years</a> to decompose in a landfill]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/21/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Make recycling a second job!  Recycling generates on an average <a href="http://www.uoregon.edu/~recycle/TRIVIA.htm" target="_blank">one job</a> for every 465 tons of materials handled each year.  That’s about 43,000 recycling jobs a year.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/22/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Buying second hand gives people a second chance.  <a href="http://www.textilerecycle.org/facts.pdf" target="_blank">Textile recycling</a> firms purchase a large percentage of their raw materials from charitable institutions, who in turn use these funds to house, feed, and train the less fortunate.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/23/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Everyone knows biking is the green way to go.  But did you also know that <a href="http://www.care2.com/greenliving/benefits-of-biking.html" target="_blank">biking can make you happy</a>?  Get out and boost your euphoria-producing hormones today!]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/24/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Next time you paint your house, choose a lighter color.  Any light color is a shade of green, since light reflects heat (dark colors absorb it), which can <a href="http://www.insuladd.com/" target="_blank">increase cooling costs by 20%</a>. ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/25/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Think twice about disposables!  It takes disposable diapers <a href="http://www.thegreenestdollar.com/2009/05/how-long-our-garbage-lasts/" target="_blank">550 years</a> to decompose in a landfill.  And we throw 18 billion of them away every year.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/26/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Try to be a better eco-citizen.  The average American uses <a href="http://www.bringrecycling.org/benefits.html" target="_blank">eight times</a> the natural resources of the average world citizen and produces five times the air pollution of the average world citizen]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/27/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Try to live a paperless life.  The world’s forests are being destroyed at the rate of one acre per second.  Every <a href="http://www.bringrecycling.org/benefits.html" target="_blank">16 minutes</a>, a forest the size of New York’s Central Park is destroyed.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/28/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Don’t put old shoes in the trash—donate them to charity!  It takes rubber boot soles <a href="http://ndep.nv.gov/nevadarecycles.gov/doc/curriculum/lesson%204%20master.pdf" target="_blank">50-80 years</a> to decompose in a landfill.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/29/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Don't kill that spider!  Spiders eat insects so they provide a natural pest control service.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/30/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Don’t put nylon materials in the trash!  It takes nylon material <a href="http://ndep.nv.gov/nevadarecycles.gov/doc/curriculum/lesson%204%20master.pdf" target="_blank">30-40 years</a> to decompose in a landfill.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>05/31/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[We've gone overboard treating the ocean as a wastebasket.  We toss 2.5 million pieces of debris into the ocean every hour.  Every square mile of ocean has over 46,000 pieces of plastic debris floating on it.
]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>06/01/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Don’t air condition an empty room.  If you have central air, <a href="http://michaelbluejay.com/electricity/cooling.html" target="_blank">close the registers</a> in rooms you aren’t using.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>06/02/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.nature.org/initiatives/climatechange/activities/art19630.html" target="_blank">Walk or bike instead</a>.  Cars produce over 20 percent of total carbon emissions in the U.S.  Walk or bike and you’ll save one pound of carbon for every mile you travel.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>06/03/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Two degrees cooler in winter or warmer in summer can reduce your CO2 load by 2,000 pounds per year.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>06/04/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Father’s Day is just around the corner.  Think outside the tie with <a href="http://www.care2.com/greenliving/green-gift-guide-for-fathers-day.html" target="_blank">green Father’s Day gift ideas</a> that show him how well he taught you the lesson of giving back.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>06/05/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Keep your grass 3-4 inches long.  Keeping grass longer in hot summer months helps keep it greener, and requires less water.  When you mow, leave some lawn clippings on the grass to reduce evaporation.   ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>06/06/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Get a <a href="http://home.howstuffworks.com/mulch-vs-bag-grass.htm" target="_blank">mulching</a> blade for your lawn mower.  Grass makes up 70% of all yard waste.  But if grass clippings are short enough, they quickly decompose and supply the soil with nitrogen and carbon, and lead to a lawn that requires less watering.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>06/07/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Mulch out methane.  Use a mulching blade and leave grass clippings on your lawn.  When yard waste is buried in <a href="http://www.howstuffworks.com/landfill.htm/printable" target="_blank">landfills</a>, where there’s little oxygen, it releases methane, a greenhouse gas with 27 times the negative environmental impact of CO2.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>06/08/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Stay cool, switch to CFL bulbs.  Your home will stay cooler in the summer with fluorescent lighting.  A fluorescent bulb generates <a href="http://www.energystar.gov/index.cfm?c=news.nr_winter2008" target="_blank">70% less heat</a> than a regular bulb.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>06/09/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[When it’s hot, fans are cool.  If you have ceiling fans or other fans, turn them on.  The blowing air can make you feel up to <a href="http://www.residential-landscape-lighting-design.com/energy_benefits_ceiling_fans.htm" target="_blank">eight degrees cooler</a> and reduce air conditioning bills by up to 40%!]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>06/10/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.xcelenergy.com/SiteCollectionDocuments/docs/60_Ways.pdf" target="_blank">Keep the air moving</a> and your energy costs down.  Air movement creates a wind chill effect.  A two mph wind will make you an 82°F day feel like it is 78°.  Ceiling fans and portable oscillating fans make a big difference.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>06/11/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Turn off lights and appliances you aren’t using!  The electricity generated by fossil fuels for a single home puts more carbon dioxide into the air than <a href="http://earth911.com/reduce/saving-energy-at-home/" target="_blank">two average cars</a>.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>06/12/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Use a low-flow showerhead and lower your carbon footprint by 350 pounds of carbon dioxide.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>06/13/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Lemon juice, dishwasher detergent and vinegar make great <a href="http://www.ehow.com/how_2184890_whiten-clothes-using-bleach.html" target="_blank">natural laundry whiteners</a>.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>06/14/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Save up your errands and run them all at once.  The fewer trips you make, the more time, CO2 and gas you save!  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>06/15/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[The average adult spends <a href="http://www.ncbuy.com/news/20010719/0-average-american-showers-for-8.html" target="_blank">eight minutes</a> in the shower, which uses 40-80 gallons of water.  How long does your teenager spend in the shower?  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>06/16/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Don’t pop frozen dishes into the oven.  Thaw them before cooking and you can save 30-50% on energy costs.  Your food will cook faster too. ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>06/17/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Pre-heat the oven only for baking.  If you’re re-heating a casserole or cooking a roast, pre-heating isn’t necessary.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>06/18/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Less is more.  You can encourage deeper plant roots by watering less often, but slowly and for longer periods.  You’ll use less water and you plants will be healthier too!  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>06/19/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Make one day a week a “no-car” day.  Forty percent of all the car trips we make are less than two miles.  Every mile you don’t drive can help reduce gas consumption and <a href="http://earth911.com/reduce/what-can-i-do-to-help-prevent-climate-change/" target="_blank">one pound</a> of carbon dioxide!]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>06/20/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.nature.org/initiatives/climatechange/activities/art19630.html" target="_blank">Act globally, eat locally</a>.   The groceries sold in the store down the street were probably flown from the other side of the world, burning fossil fuels the entire trip.  Locally grown food is fresher, healthier and better for our climate.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>06/21/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.nature.org/initiatives/climatechange/activities/art19630.html" target="_blank">Check your tires monthly</a>.  Properly inflated tires get better gas mileage.  At $3 a gallon, the average car owner is spending <a href="http://www.cmu.edu/cmnews/extra///050921_tire.html" target="_blank">$432 for gas</a> they don’t need to.  And each gallon of gas saved means 20 pounds of carbon dioxide aren’t produced.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>06/22/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[When you’re out cutting grass, make sure the condenser unit on your air conditioner is not blocked.   Grasses or other landscaping and/or debris restrict airflow and drain electricity]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>06/23/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.fueleconomy.gov/feg/driveHabits.shtml" target="_blank">Drive smarter</a>.  Get higher mpg with less greenhouse gas by going easy on the brakes and gas pedal, avoiding hard accelerations, reducing how much time you let your car idle and taking any unnecessary weight out of your trunk.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>06/24/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Avoid buying products with excessive packaging.  When you check the price, make it a point to also evaluate the packaging.  Not only will you save money, you’ll also help the environment.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>06/25/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.fueleconomy.gov/feg/maintain.shtml" target="_blank">Tune up your mpg</a> and your carbon footprint.  Fixing an out of tune car can boost gas mileage by an average of four percent.  Fixing a serious maintenance problem, such as a faulty oxygen sensor, can boost mileage by as much as 40%.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>06/26/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Reducing your garbage by 10% reduces carbon dioxide emissions by <a href="http://www.cutco2.org/what-can-i-do.php" target="_blank">1,200 pounds</a>.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>06/27/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Wash in cold water.  Your clothes will get just as clean and you’ll reduce your carbon footprint by <a href="http://earth911.com/blog/2007/04/02/what-can-i-do-to-help-prevent-climate-change/" target="_blank">500 pounds</a> a year.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>06/28/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Make the most of your hot water by insulating your tank, keeping the temperature at or below 120° and installing a timer to turn it off at night when you aren’t using it.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>06/29/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Grow your recycling footprint.  You can save up to <a href="http://earth911.com/what-can-i-do-to-help-prevent-climate-change/" target="_blank">2,400 pounds</a> of carbon dioxide each year just by recycling half of your household waste.  Buying products with recycled content saves energy, resources and landfill space.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>06/30/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[In the U.S., approximately 6.6 tons of greenhouse gases are emitted per person every year.  Most of these emissions, <a href="http://earth911.com/reduce/what-can-i-do-to-help-prevent-climate-change/" target="_blank">about 82%</a>, are from burning fossil fuels to generate electricity and power our cars.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/01/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[More than 100 million trees are destroyed each year to produce junk mail; that’s the equivalent of clear-cutting the entire Rocky Mountain National Park every four months.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/02/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Pre-cycle!  <a href="http://www.ilacsd.org/pdf/brochures/JunkMailReduction%20Kit.pdf" target="_blank">Eliminate junk mail</a> by calling 1-888-5-OPTOUT, or fill out an online form <a href="http://www.optoutprescreen.com/" target="_blank">here</a>.  OptOut is a joint venture of the four major credit bureaus (Equifax, Experian, Innovis, and TransUnion).  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/03/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.ilacsd.org/pdf/brochures/JunkMailReduction%20Kit.pdf" target="_blank">De-list yourself</a>!  About 28 billion gallons of water are wasted to produce and recycle junk mail each year.  One of the biggest culprits is the Direct Marketing Association’s mailing list.  You can remove your name by writing to the <a href="https://www.dmachoice.org/dma/member/home.action;jsessionid=D725D8388AE15E7E12F300FDF3502368.tomcat2" target="_blank">Direct Marketing Association (DMA)</a>.   In your letter, request deletion of your name and address from all mailing and marketing lists.  Provide them with all possible ways of spelling your name, as well as the names of anyone else at your address wanting to opt out of junk mail.  Be sure to sign and date your letter.  MPS will retain your information in their database for five years and will mail this information to business subscribers four times a year.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/04/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.ilacsd.org/pdf/brochures/JunkMailReduction%20Kit.pdf" target="_blank">Call off the catalogs</a>.  The average American wastes about 70 hours a year dealing with junk mail.  You can stop unsolicited catalogues in the mail simply by calling the company's 800 number on the label.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/05/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.ilacsd.org/pdf/brochures/JunkMailReduction%20Kit.pdf" target="_blank">Go AWOL on AOL</a> (America On-Line): Stop those pesky discs from littering your mailbox by calling 1-800-605-4297 (24 hours a day).  Tell them your first name is "current", last name "resident".]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/06/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.ilacsd.org/pdf/brochures/JunkMailReduction%20Kit.pdf" target="_blank">Clear out Clearinghouse junk mail</a>.  You can get Publisher's Clearinghouse Sweepstakes to stop clogging your mailbox by calling 1-800-645-9242 (8:30 am to 8:30 EST), sending a fax to 1-800-453-0272, or writing to Christopher L.  Irving, Senior Director of Consumer &amp; Privacy Affairs, 382 Channel Drive, Port Washington, New York, 11050 ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/07/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Junk mail accounts for the majority of an average household’s paper waste.  Enter to Win your freedom from American Family Sweepstakes.  You can tell them to stop bothering you by calling 1-800-237-2400.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/08/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Call off the lists.  All that mail that comes with pictures of missing children can be stopped by calling 1-860-285-6100.  You can also send a postcard to "ADVO Consumer Assistance, PO Box 249, Windsor, CT 06095-4176".]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/09/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Hate those envelopes full of coupons?  So does the recycling center.  Next time you get one, save the mailing label and go to <a href="http://www.valpak.com/coupons/home" target="_blank">Valpak’s website</a> to removal your name from their mailing list.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/10/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Think those Carol Wright junk mailings are just wrong?  Call 1-800-67-TARGET to get off the list.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/11/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Sign up permanently to halt catalog mailings from association members.  Email <a href="mailto:abacusoptout@epsilon.com">abacusoptout@epsilon.com</a> with your full name and current address.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/12/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Don’t have the time to go through all the individual steps required to stop junk mail from littering your mailbox?  You can pay $41 to a junk mail removal service that will eliminate most all of your junk mail (for five years) at <a href="http://www.41pounds.org/" target="_blank">http://www.41pounds.org/</a>.  A nice plus…they donate ⅓ of their fee to environmental causes.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/13/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Send the kids outside to play!  Video game consoles consume an estimated <a href="http://www.scientificamerican.com/article.cfm?id=being-green-11-enviro-habits" target="_blank">16 billion</a> kilowatt-hours of electricity annually—about four times the output of Hoover Dam.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/14/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Put a lid on it!  Putting a lid on the pot whenever you boil water <a href="http://www.pbs.org/wgbh/nova/energy/lid.html" target="_blank">saves time, energy and money</a>.   If every U.S. household did this just once, we’d save up to $2,212,175.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/15/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Don’t air condition an empty house.  In summer, when no one is home, program your thermostat to go up to 85 degrees.  You’ll reduce the need for air conditioning and save energy!  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/16/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Unplug cell phone chargers.  <a href="http://www.seastudios.org/climate-friendly_checklist.pdf" target="_blank">Only 5%</a> of the power a cell phone charger drains actually performs the charge.  If you’re not using it, unplug it!  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/17/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Switch to tap water.  You can make a big impact by breaking the bottle-a-day habit.  <a href="http://www.newdream.org/water/calculator.php" target="_blank">How much?</a>  Drinking one 16-ounce bottle a day, 365 days a year, adds 68 lbs of CO2 to the atmosphere, wastes 37 mega joules of energy, and requires nine gallons of oil to manufacture, process, fill, transport to market and process the waste.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/18/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Buy a reusable water bottle.  You’ll not only save energy, oil and CO2, you’ll save a lot of money.  Drinking the recommended amount of water (8-12 cups a day) out of the tap costs just a dollar a year.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/19/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[In summer, plan your laundry, dishwashing and other moisture producing activities for early morning or late evening when it’s cooler.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/20/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Is the damper on your fireplace closed?  In the summer, an <a href="http://www.energyquest.ca.gov/saving_energy/index.html" target="_blank">open fireplace damper</a> can let cool air escape.  It’s like having a window open!]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/21/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Make sure your motor oil makes the grade.  Using the manufacturer's recommended grade of motor oil can improve gas mileage by 1-2%.  Look for motor oil that says "Energy Conserving" on the API performance symbol to be sure it contains friction-reducing additives.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/22/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Counterintuitive but true: car washes use less water than driveway washes.  Yep.  You’ll save 35-95 gallons per wash.  And if you go to a car wash that uses recycled water, you can conserve even more.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/23/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Bottled water like <a href="http://www.fastcompany.com/magazine/117/features-message-in-a-bottle.html" target="_blank">Fiji</a> or Evian, can cost up to 10,000 times as much as tap water.  Even purified water, like Aquafina, is nearly 2,500 times more expensive to drink.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/24/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Hot tip:  water your yard in the coolest part of the day.  It’s better for your plants and you can get away with watering less, because less is lost to evaporation from the sun’s heat.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/25/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Summertime <a href="http://www.residential-landscape-lighting-design.com/energy_benefits_ceiling_fans.htm" target="_blank">Fan Plan</a>: In the summer, reverse your ceiling fan to run counterclockwise.  This will push cool air down and help lower your air conditioning bills by as much as 40%.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/26/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Cool hot foods before putting them in the fridge.  Cooling hot foods down first will save your refrigerator a lot of work.  The USDA rule of thumb on food safety is to refrigerate food that has been at room temperature more than two hours.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/27/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Do you use decorative outdoor natural gas lamps?  Just eight natural gas lamps burning year-round use as much natural gas as it takes to heat an average size home during an entire winter.  Replace them with <a href="http://electrical.hardwarestore.com/learning/8-simple-steps-to-saving-energy.aspx" target="_blank">high-intensity discharge (HID) or low-pressure sodium outdoor lights</a>.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/28/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Outdoor lights are a great use of compact fluorescent light bulbs because CFLs last 10 times longer.  Live in a cold climate?  Buy a lamp with a cold weather ballast—standard CFLs don’t work well below 40°F.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/29/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Blue light special:  save energy and <a href="http://www.xcelenergy.com/SiteCollectionDocuments/docs/60_Ways.pdf" target="_blank">turn off the pilot light on your gas furnace over the summer</a>.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/30/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Don’t dump trash, lawn clippings or chemicals into <a href="http://www.epa.gov/weatherchannel/stormwater.html" target="_blank">storm drains</a>.  Storm drains empty into rivers and streams that eventually flow to the oceans.  Whatever is in there will be carried untreated to water bodies that people and wildlife depend on.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>07/31/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Did you know it's more efficient to <a href="http://planetgreen.discovery.com/home-garden/fill-fridge-energy-efficient.html" target="_blank">keep your freezer and refrigerator full</a> than half full?  It takes less energy to keep the air cold when there is more to fill the space (it doesn’t have to be food; containers of water will do the trick).
]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/01/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.greenercars.org/drivingtips.htm" target="_blank">Take your pedal off the metal</a>.  The more you anticipate stops and let your vehicle coast down the more you can eliminate pollution, wasted gas, and unnecessary wear on your brakes.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/02/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.greenercars.org/drivingtips.htm" target="_blank">Avoid rush hour</a>.  Stop-and-go driving is not only frustrating; it burns more gas and creates more smog-forming pollutants.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/03/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.greenercars.org/drivingtips.htm" target="_blank">Turn your car air conditioner off or down</a>.  Operating the air conditioner on "Max" can reduce energy usage by roughly 5-25% compared to not using it.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/04/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.greenercars.org/drivingtips.htm" target="_blank">Combine errands</a>.  Warmed-up engines generate a lot less air pollution, so when you’re out doing one errand, see what else you can accomplish nearby.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/05/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[If you have a manual transmission, shift up as soon as possible.  Running in a higher gear decreases the rpm and decreases fuel use and engine wear.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/06/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.greenercars.org/drivingtips.htm" target="_blank">Open car windows and vents</a> before you resort to the air conditioner.  It increases fuel consumption, increases NOx emissions in some vehicles, and involves environmentally damaging fluids.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/07/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Stop the top off.  <a href="http://www.greenercars.org/drivingtips.htm" target="_blank">Don't overfill the gas tank</a> or try to top it off beyond where the automatic nozzle clicks off.  Spilled gasoline evaporates to aggravate smog formation and can leak into groundwater.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/08/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Be nozzle-wise.  <a href="http://www.greenercars.org/drivingtips.htm" target="_blank">Look for gas stations that have vapor-recovery nozzles</a> (those black, accordion-looking plastic devices attached to the nozzle) whenever you can.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/09/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Trade in your gas-guzzler.  Increasing your fuel economy will increase your saving and lower your carbon footprint.  If gas is $2.60 a gallon and you drive 15,000 miles a year, increasing your mpg from 22 to 37 will save $719 per year.  <a href="http://www.fueleconomy.gov/Feg/savemoney.shtml" target="_blank">Calculate your savings here</a>. ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/10/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Want to buy a hybrid but don’t want sticker shock?  Buy it used]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/11/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.xcelenergy.com/SiteCollectionDocuments/docs/60_Ways.pdf" target="_blank">Check your insulation</a>.  If you have six inches or less on your walls, floors, attic or ceiling, adding insulation will save you significant energy and money.  One inch of insulation has the “heat stopping” ability of 46 inches of concrete.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/12/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Reset the temperature in your refrigerator and freezer.  Your settings only need to be 36-40°F for the fridge and 0-5°F for the freezer.  Fridges set 10° lower than necessary (or freezers set 5° lower) can require as much 20-25% more energy.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/13/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Take the water meter challenge.  <a href="http://www.h2ouse.org/resources/meter/index.cfm" target="_blank">Read your meter</a> at the beginning and the end of your typical day.  Then challenge yourself to cut your water consumption drastically and read it again.  Compare the two totals and see how much water and money you can save!  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/14/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.greenercars.org/drivingtips.htm" target="_blank">Unload your load</a>.  An extra 100 pounds can reduce your car’s fuel economy by about one percent.  Take those golf clubs out of your trunk!]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/15/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Parking in the shade in summer doesn’t just keep your car cool; it minimizes the amount of fuel that evaporates.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/16/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Gauge your savings.  Buy a tire gauge and check your tires monthly to make sure they are properly inflated.  You can <a href="http://www.fueleconomy.gov/feg/maintain.shtml" target="_blank">improve gas mileage</a> by about 3.3%, which comes out to about ei]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/17/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.xcelenergy.com/SiteCollectionDocuments/docs/60_Ways.pdf" target="_blank">Keep your air ducts airtight</a>.  Ducts that move air to-and-from a furnace, central air conditioner, or heat pump can be huge energy wasters.  <a href="http://www.energystar.gov/index.cfm?c=home_improvement.hm_improvement_ducts" target="_blank">Sealing and insulating ducts</a> can improve efficiency by as much as 20 percent or more.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/18/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.xcelenergy.com/SiteCollectionDocuments/docs/60_Ways.pdf" target="_blank">Adding a storm window</a> to a single-pane window can cut heat loss by as much as 50%.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/19/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Improve your health and the health of our planet with <a href="http://www.meatlessmonday.com/" target="_blank">Meatless Mondays</a>.   Cutting meat consumption by 15%, just one day a week, can make a big difference in the amount of gasoline and water consumed, not to mention your cholesterol.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/20/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Don’t buy new toys for your kids, rent them instead!  Kids outgrow their toys faster than their clothes.  Save energy and money by renting them instead!  <a href="http://www.babyplays.com/" target="_blank">BabyPlays</a> is one service, but there are probably similar options in your community; check out the <a href="http://www.itla-toylibraries.org/" target="_blank">International Toy Lending Association</a>.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/21/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Recycle your aluminum cans.  It is the ultimate sustainable choice, because <a href="http://www.cancentral.com/funFacts.cfm" target="_blank">aluminum</a> never wears out.  It can be recycled forever.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/22/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.energysavers.gov/your_home/water_heating/index.cfm/mytopic=13110" target="_blank">Install a water heater timer</a>.  If you have an electric water heater, you can save an additional 5–12% of energy with a timer that turns off your water heater off at night when you don't need hot water and/or during peak demand times.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/23/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.ehow.com/how_2026039_save-energy-fridge.html" target="_blank">Clean your refrigerator coils</a>.  Dust on your coils prevents your refrigerator from running efficiently, costing energy and money.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/24/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Clean out your cleaning chemicals.  Before modern technology gave us an entire aisle of products to choose from, grandma got most jobs done with the original green cleaners: <a href="http://www.treehugger.com/files/2007/07/62_uses_for_vin.php" target="_blank">www.treehugger.com</a>. ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/25/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Back to School green shopping Tip #1:  Take inventory and avoid duplicates.  How many pencils, notebooks, etc do you already have on hand?  Is a new backpack or lunch bag really necessary?  Make a list of what you need and stick to it.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/26/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Back to School green shopping Tip #2:  Green up your school gear with <a href="http://www.treehugger.com/files/2007/07/sharpen_write_p.php" target="_blank">biodegradable pencils</a>, <a href="http://www.treehugger.com/files/2007/04/pilots_begreen.php" target="_blank">refillable pens</a>, and recycled versions of both.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/27/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Back to School green shopping Tip #3:  Buy used textbooks online (<a href="http://www.amazon.com" target="_blank">Amazon</a> and <a href="http://www.ecampus.com" target="_blank">eCampus</a> are very popular) or <a href="http://earth911.com/news/2008/12/29/the-rules-of-rental/" target="_blank">rent</a> your textbooks.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/28/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Back to School green shopping Tip #4:  Resist buying things like glue sticks in bulk if you know you'll only need one or two between now and next spring.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/29/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Every fall kids go back to school and pests come back into the house.  Chemical pesticides are poisons and can be very dangerous.  Know your <a href="http://www.epa.gov/pesticides/controlling/index.htm" target="_blank">pest prevention and non-chemical pest control options</a> and make sure you are practicing <a href="http://www.epa.gov/pesticides/controlling/index.htm" target="_blank">safe pest control</a>.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/30/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Think outside the brown bag.  Pack lunches in a washable, reusable PVC-free tote.  Bag the baggies and plastic wrap in favor of reusable containers.  Pass on plastic bottles containing <a href="http://www.treehugger.com/files/2008/04/bpa-in-water.php" target="_blank">Bisphenol A</a> (BPA), a hormone-disrupting chemical.  Metal is a greener choice.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>08/31/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Don’t stand idly by!  Those school buses lined up in front of the school with their engines running waste fuel, pollute the air and endanger children, who are more sensitive to diesel exhaust (it causes respiratory problems and worsens allergies and asthma).  Convince school officials to adopt a <a href="http://www.epa.gov/epahome/hi-fall.htm" target="_blank">no-idling policy</a>.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>09/01/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Give your dry cleaner the sniff test.  Odor is a sure sign they are using harmful petrochemical industrial solvent.  <a href="http://www.greenearthcleaning.com/storeLocator.aspx" target="_blank">Locate a truly green dry cleaner</a> using the GreenEarth Cleaning process or CO2.  If you must take clothes to a conventional cleaner, be sure to air them outside before wearing or putting in your closet.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>09/02/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Ever heard of professional wet cleaning?  A water-based, eco-friendly alternative to dry cleaning, it’s a good choice IF your cleaner isn’t using toxic chemicals to remove stains and rinsing them down the drain.  Also ask:  how often do they send out items that can’t be cleaned in water to dry cleaners using petrochemicals?]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>09/03/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Cans can make a difference.  Recycling aluminum uses <a href="http://earth911.com/reduce/energy-costs-and-conservation-facts" target=_blank">95% less energy</a> than virgin aluminum.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>09/04/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Thaw frozen foods in the refrigerator instead of on the counter.  They help keep the fridge cool as they thaw.    ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>09/05/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Recycling does a ton of good.  Recycling one ton of aluminum saves the equivalent in energy of <a href="http://www.sustain.ucla.edu/handbook/article.asp?parentid=3465" target="_blank">2,350 gallons</a> of gasoline.  This is the same amount of electricity the typical home would use over a period of 10 years.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>09/06/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://planetgreen.discovery.com/food-health/pvc-vinyl-shower-curtain.html" target="_blank">Take care of your vinyl shower curtain</a>.  A <a href="http://www.canada.com/topics/news/story.html?id=dfe49cb3-b104-4d4a-a449-14e4faf17e2b" target="_blank">study on vinyl shower curtains</a> reveals that new vinyl shower curtains can release toxins that are harmful to your health.  If your shower curtain no longer has a smell, take care of it so that you won’t need to replace it.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>09/07/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://electrical.hardwarestore.com/learning/8-simple-steps-to-saving-energy.aspx" target="_blank">Install motion sensor outdoor lights</a>.   Outdoor lights with a combined photocell and motion sensor will create energy savings by only turning on at night when someone is present.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>09/08/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.xcelenergy.com/SiteCollectionDocuments/docs/60_Ways.pdf" target="_blank">Check your furnace filter</a> once a month and change it when it looks dirty.  At a minimum, change the filter every three months.  A dirty filter slows down airflow and wastes energy by making the system work harder to keep you warm or cool.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>09/09/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.xcelenergy.com/SiteCollectionDocuments/docs/60_Ways.pdf" target="_blank">Check the seal on your fridge</a> by closing the door on a piece of paper.  If it slides out easily your seal (or your fridge) may need replacing as it is letting cold air out.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>09/10/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://greenhomeguide.com/know-how/article/selecting-green-paint" target="_blank">Buy latex, water-based paint instead of enamel</a>.   Most every brand of paint offers a low odor, water-based alternative to environmentally harmful oil-based paints.  When you are done, make sure you take steps to <a href="http://www.ehow.com/how_4579240_dispose-latex-paint.html" target="_blank">properly dispose of your latex paint cans</a>. ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>09/11/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Charge your cell phone during the day instead of overnight.  Most mobile phones only need about two hours to fully charge.  Plugging in your charger at night creates a lot of wasted energy!]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>09/12/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Recycle that old hairbrush!  It makes a great tool for cleaning room air conditioner coils—a good way to make sure your air conditioner isn’t pulling more energy than it needs to.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>09/13/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Next time you feel like reading a new book, borrow it from the library or a friend instead of buying a new copy.  It’s is a great way to reduce waste and reuse materials.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>09/14/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Before you buy that tool you need, check to see if your city has a <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_tool-lending_libraries" target="_blank">tool lending library</a>.  Many cities offer basic hand, gardening, landscaping, and construction tools to local residents, often for free with your library card.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>09/15/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[If you live in the city and don’t use your car very often, consider <a href="http://planetgreen.discovery.com" target="_blank">car sharing</a>.  Car-sharing services like <a href="http://www.zipcar.com/" target="_blank">Zipcar</a> and others you'll find from the <a href="http://www.carsharing.net/" target="_blank">Car Sharing Network</a> give you hassle-free access to a car.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>09/16/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Make one day a week laundry day.  Washing full loads saves big on utility costs.   <a href="http://www.xcelenergy.com/SiteCollectionDocuments/docs/60_Ways.pdf" target="_blank">Drying loads consecutively</a> requires less energy because it leverages the built up heat in your dryer.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>09/17/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Have a <a href="http://planetgreen.discovery.com/go-green/weddings/top-green-weddings-tips.html" target="_blank">green wedding</a>.  With the average cost of a wedding today running about $20,000, weddings have a huge environmental and economic cost.  Make a green statement about how you want to spend the rest of your life.  It’s easier than you think!  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>09/18/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Plant trees and bushes around your air conditioner to create shade for it in the summer and it will run <a href="http://www.xcelenergy.com/SiteCollectionDocuments/docs/60_Ways.pdf" target="_blank">up to 10%</a> more efficiently.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>09/19/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Whenever you are drawing water from the tap, use the cold water instead of the hot. ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>09/20/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Using washable rags instead of paper towels for household cleaning saves trees and money]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>09/21/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Organize your refrigerator and cabinets.  Knowing what you have prevents you from wasting food!  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>09/22/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Evergreens can green up your utility bill.  Planted to the north and northwest of your home, evergreens will help block winter winds and prevent cold drafts.  If your house faces cold winter winds, a buffer of evergreen shrubs planted around the entry to your home will minimize the chill.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>09/23/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.xcelenergy.com/SiteCollectionDocuments/docs/60_Ways.pdf" target="_blank">Use the dishwasher</a> if you have one.  It uses less hot water than washing by hand.  Use the air-dry setting for drying to save energy.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>09/24/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Buying a new appliance?  Make sure they are <a href="http://www.energystar.gov/index.cfm?c=products.pr_find_es_products" target="_blank">Energy Star</a> products.  It is an easy way to make a difference to the planet and your utility budget.   ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>09/25/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Reduce, recycle, <a href="http://planetgreen.discovery.com/go-green/green-laundry/green-laundry-basics.html" target="_blank">re-wear</a>. Green up your laundry impact and lighten your load with “re-wear”—wearing everything you can more than once.  The average home does more than 400 loads of laundry a year—cutting it by half will save big on time, energy and money.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>09/26/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Create your own low-flush toilet.  Fill up a plastic bottle filled with water and drop it into the tank of your toilet.  With every flush, you’ll be saving that much water to refill the tank.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>09/27/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[The best things in life aren’t things.  Giving <a href="http://www.care2.com/greenliving/25-great-consumer-less-gift-ideas.html" target="_blank">gifts of your time, your talents</a> or donating <a href="http://greenliving.about.com/od/thegreenfamily/tp/green_charitable_donation.htm" target="_blank">money to a good cause</a> in someone’s name are really thoughtful and very green.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>09/28/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Take the plunge, go <a href="http://www.beyondpesticides.org/pesticidefreelawns/resources/index.htm" target="_blank">pesticide-free</a>!  Replace the pesticides you use on your lawn with natural products that work just as well or better.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>09/29/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Find out if water leaks are draining you.  Turn off all the taps in your house, then <a href="http://www.h2ouse.org/resources/meter/index.cfm" target="_blank">check your water meter</a>.  If it is still turning, you likely have a leak somewhere.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>09/30/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Buy a share in a community supported agriculture program.  CSA shares buy you weekly boxes of fresh, locally grown produce.  Cost?  About $300-400 for a 24-26 week growing season (many CSAs let you buy weekly or monthly).  Check <a href="http://www.nal.usda.gov/afsic/csa/" target="_blank">Alternative Farming Systems Information Center</a>, <a href="http://www.foodroutes.org/" target="_blank">Food Routes</a> and <a href="http://www.localharvest.org/" target="_blank">LocalHarvest</a> to find a CSA near you.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/01/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Breast Cancer Awareness Month is a good time to give the gift of a rainforest tree.  Rainforests are home to many plants that help fight cancer.  <a href="https://secure.nrdconline.org/site/Donation2?df_id=1757&amp;1757.donation=form1&amp;JServSessionIdr004=thf0ugey12.app306a" target="_blank">For $10 the Natural Resources Defense Council will plant a rainforest tree</a> in honor of a friend or family member and send a personalized E-card message of support.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/02/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Help fight breast cancer, go Paperless For the Cure.  The U.S. National Cancer Institute has identified 3000 plants that are active against cancer cells; <a href="http://www.rain-tree.com/facts.htm" target="_blank">70%</a> of these plants are found in the rainforest.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/03/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Think Pink.  Live Green.  <a href="http://www.cancercare.on.ca/pcs/prevention/bodywtexer/" target="_blank">More than ⅓ of cancers</a> can be prevented by eating a balanced diet, staying physically active, and maintaining a healthy body weight.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/04/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Step up the fight against cancer by stepping up your commitment to recycle paper.  Twenty-five percent of the active ingredients in today's cancer-fighting drugs come from organisms found <a href="http://www.rain-tree.com/facts.htm" target="_blank">only in the rainforest</a>.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/05/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/idUSTRE52C58S20090314" target="_blank">Studies suggest</a> that women who get plenty of mushrooms and green tea in their diets may have a lower risk of developing breast cancer!]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/06/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[If you or a loved one has survived breast cancer, be sure to get plenty of exercise and drink green tea.  <a href="http://ww5.komen.org/ExternalNewsArticle.aspx?newsID=44570" target="_blank">Studies show</a> these lifestyle factors may help prevent depression.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/07/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Most women know that breastfeeding is best for babies and the planet, but did you know that women who choose to breast-feed might also <a href="http://www.cancer.org/docroot/CRI/content/CRI_2_4_2X_Can_breast_cancer_be_prevented_5.asp" target="_blank">reduce their breast cancer risk</a>?]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/08/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Breast Cancer Awareness Month is a good time to de-toxify your life.  Chemicals used in everyday products can be a health concern.  Check out this searchable index to <a href="http://www.simplesteps.org/chemicals" target="_blank">learn what chemicals are toxic and should be avoided</a>.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/09/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Recycling can take you far.  Since 1972 <a href="http://www.cancentral.com/funFacts.cfm" target="_blank">19 million tons</a> of aluminum cans have been recycled in the U.S.  These cans, placed end-to end, could stretch to the moon and back 174 times.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/10/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[BYOB:  Bring your own bags.  The typical American family accumulates 60 permanently polluting plastic bags after just four grocery-shopping trips.  High quality reusable bags are everywhere these days.  Keep yours handy and remember to use them.  Many grocery stores offer a 5-10 cent credit for each bag you bring.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/11/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Purchase your power from renewable energy sources!  <a href="http://apps3.eere.energy.gov/greenpower/buying/buying_power.shtml" target="_blank">Find out find out what green power options are available in your state</a>. ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/12/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Be Green.  Get free stuff.  Make someone else’s trash your treasure.  Join the <a href="http://www.freecycle.org/" target="_blank">Freecycle Network</a> and find free stuff you can put to good re-use.  Their service keeps more than 300 tons a day out of landfills!  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/13/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[In cold weather, when you go to sleep or leave home for an extended time, set the thermostat back to 55°, or turn it off.  For every one degree you turn down the thermostat in the winter <a href="http://earth911.com/location/california/flex-your-power/" target="_blank">you’ll save up to 5%</a> on your heating costs!]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/14/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Always use cold water for the RINSE cycle.  Rinsing in warm water costs an extra <a href="http://michaelbluejay.com/electricity/laundry.html" target="_blank">.18¢ a load</a> and it doesn’t get your clothes any cleaner.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/15/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Two weeks until Halloween!  Why not make an eco-original costume out of materials you already have lying around?  You find lots of <a href="http://www.coolest-homemade-costumes.com/" target="_blank">homemade costume ideas online</a>!  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/16/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[No matter where you set your thermostat dial, two degrees cooler in the winter or warmer in the summer can mean a reduction of <a href="http://earth911.com/reduce/what-can-i-do-to-help-prevent-climate-change/" target="_blank">2,000 pounds</a> of carbon dioxide per year.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/17/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Cruise to gas savings with cruise control.  Believe it or not, <a href="http://www.edmunds.com/advice/fueleconomy/articles/106842/article.html" target="_blank">studies prove you can save up to 14% on long trips</a>.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/18/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.brighthub.com/environment/green-living/articles/14917.aspx" target="_blank">Solar dry your laundry</a>!  Hanging your clothes up to dry saves a lot of energy, makes your clothes smell great and helps clothes last longer.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/19/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[We can do better.  The average American family recycles <a href="http://www.cancentral.com/funFacts.cfm" target="_blank">150 six packs</a> of aluminum cans a year.  But only one out of every two cans Americans consume are actually recycled.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/20/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Open a window while weather permits. Improved insulation in our homes and offices is great for energy conservation, but not necessarily <a href="http://www.epa.gov/iaq/pubs/insidest.html" target="_blank">indoor air quality</a>.  Fresh air flowing in keeps toxins flowing out.  This is especially important when cleaning your home.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/21/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Reduce your water heater temperature to 120%.  Turning it down not only saves money, it also slows mineral buildup and corrosion in your water heater and pipes, helping them <a href="http://www.energysavers.gov/your_home/water_heating/index.cfm/mytopic=13090" target="_blank">last longer</a> and operate at maximum efficiency.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/22/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[In cold weather, when you go to sleep or leave home for an extended time, set the thermostat back to 55°, or turn it off. ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/23/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Make your own triple pane windows.  <a href="http://www.xcelenergy.com/SiteCollectionDocuments/docs/60_Ways.pdf">Add a storm window</a> to a double pane window and cut your heat loss by 25% (75% over single pane).  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/24/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Make it a point to <a href="http://earth911.com/glass/benefits-of-glass-recycling/" target="_blank">recycle your glass</a>!  Glass is one of the easiest things to recycle and one of the hardest things to decompose.  That glass jar of salsa you just threw out?  It’s probably going to be there millions of years from now.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/25/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Try <a href="http://home.ivillage.com/cleanandorganize/cleaning/0,,scvq-2,00.html" target="_blank">natural air fresheners and home scents</a>.  Also, <a href="http://green.yahoo.com/blog/huddlergreenhome/29/how-to-improve-your-indoor-air-quality.html" target="_blank">plants make a great filter for interior air</a>.  Any broad green leaf plant will do (English Ivy and Peace Lilies are favorite choices).]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/26/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Choose soap and water over antibacterial and antimicrobial 'cleaners' whenever you can.  The more exclusively we rely on these products, the more we risk breeding "<a href="http://www.ewg.org/node/26872" target="_blank">super germs</a>," or chemical resistant bacteria.  Soap and water works just as well as antibacterial soaps and hand cleansers.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/27/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Strip energy consumption with power strips.  Did you know your “phantom load”—the energy drain on appliances and devices that aren’t actually in use—is 5-15% of your monthly electric bill?  Power strips with on/off switches make it easy to make sure the power is really turned off.   ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/28/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Reduce, reuse, recharge!  Rechargeable batteries cost a little more than disposable batteries, but save money in the end because they can be recharged up to <a href="http://www.uoregon.edu/~recycle/TRIVIA.htm" target="_blank">1,000 times</a>!  Take care of them and they can last up to 10 years!  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/29/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[So you just changed the ink on your printer…ahem, where is the old one?  If it’s in the trash, chances are you just sent hazardous waste to the landfill.  Ink companies make them easy to recycle with instructions, envelopes and free postage.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/30/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Did you know most athletic shoes take 1,000 years to degrade in a landfill?  They make great dog toys, or you recycle them with one of the many <a href="http://www.runtheplanet.com/shoes/selection/recycle.asp" target="_blank">organizations that recycle shoes</a>.  Nike’s <a href="http://www.nikereuseashoe.com/" target="_blank">Re-Use a Shoe</a> program lets you drop off up to 10 pairs of shoes at a time.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>10/31/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[When you take the kids out to trick or treat tonight, make it a teachable trip.  Carry two bags: one for treats and one to collect discarded candy wrappers and costumes.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>11/01/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Trees beautify your yard and cut your energy costs.  A deciduous (leafy) tree creates shade to cool your house in the summer, and after its leaves fall in winter, lets sunlight in to help warm your house.  Late winter is a good time to plant.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>11/02/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Halloween is over.  Donate those costumes!  Take them to a local children's hospital or charity shop.  Costumes are always a treat for kids less fortunate!  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>11/03/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Just two months left to claim green tax deductions for this year.   If you are thinking about making energy saving improvements in your home or car, learn more about the <a href="http://www.fueleconomy.gov/feg/taxcenter.shtml" target="_blank">tax incentives for buying a green car</a> and <a href="http://www.energystar.gov/index.cfm?c=tax_credits.tx_index" target="_blank">tax credits you can earn for home improvements</a>.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>11/04/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[How green is your vote?  If knowing your candidates position on environmental issues and legislative progress against environmental priorities is important to you, the <a href="http://www.lcv.org/" target="_blank">League of Conservation Voters</a> a great resource.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>11/05/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Did you know burning candles could emit carcinogens and neurotoxins?  Burn safely—select eco-friendly soy, palm oil or beeswax varieties.  Check to be sure they don’t contain stearic acid (an animal-derived fat from meatpacking plants) or synthetic fragrances classified as VOCs.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>11/06/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.nature.org/initiatives/climatechange/activities/art19630.html" target="_blank">Teleconference more; fly less</a>.  You will save time, money, and carbon emissions.  Airplanes account for 12% of all transportation sector emissions.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>11/07/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[No matter what kind of winter we’re having, according to the National Academy of Sciences, the Earth’s surface temperature has risen by about <a href="http://earth911.com/reduce/climate-change-and-you/" target="_blank">1° Fahrenheit</a> in the past century, with accelerated warming during the past two decades.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>11/08/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Clean up with cans:  recycling aluminum <a href="http://earth911.com/reduce/energy-costs-and-conservation-facts/" target="_blank">reduces air pollution by 95%</a> and water pollution by 97% versus producing aluminum from natural resources.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>11/09/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[If you live in a warm climate, light-colored cars are green.  Lighter colors reflect heat (and dark colors absorb it), so they require less air conditioning to cool down.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>11/10/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.greenercars.org/drivingtips.htm" target="_blank">Drive green</a>.  The more "jack rabbit" starts and aggressive driving you do, the more gas you waste and pollution you cause.  You can save up to <a href="http://www.edmunds.com/advice/fueleconomy/articles/106842/article.html" target="_blank">37% on gas mileage by eliminating aggressive driving</a>.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>11/11/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[It’s easy being green when you pay bills online.  Invest an hour in setting up free online or automatic bill pay and you will save a lot of time, paper and money (no more stamps or late fees!).  Feel better using a service?  Try <a href="http://quicken.intuit.com/" target="_blank">Quicken</a>, <a href="http://www.paytrust.com/" target="_blank">Pay Trust</a> or <a href="http://www.myezbills.com/" target="_blank">EZBills</a>.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>11/12/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Do you own a paper shredder?  You can do more with shredded paper than recycle it.  Reuse it for packing, stuffing gift bags, lining Easter baskets and feeding compost piles.  Makes an excellent fire starter too.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>11/13/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Seal the deal with <a href="http://electrical.hardwarestore.com/learning/8-simple-steps-to-saving-energy.aspx" target="_blank">permanent weather stripping</a>.  Stopping air from escaping through small cracks and crevices can save you up to 15% in heating and cooling costs.  A 1/8" space between a standard exterior door and its threshold is equivalent to a two square inch hole in the wall!  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>11/14/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Stopping your car for more than a minute?  Turn it off.  You can save up to 19% by avoiding excessive idling.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>11/15/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Weather stripping will help you reduce energy leaks and bills this winter.  How much will you need?  Add the perimeter of all windows and doors to be weather stripped then add 5-10%.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>11/16/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://electrical.hardwarestore.com/learning/8-simple-steps-to-saving-energy.aspx" target="_blank">Install a programmable thermostat</a>.  You can save as much as 10% a year on your heating and cooling bills by simply installing an automatic setback thermostat.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>11/17/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[The poop on poop patrol:  make sure the bags you use to clean up after your dog are biodegradable.  Otherwise you are putting 100% biodegradable material in a bag that would take 100 years to decompose!  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>11/18/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Dispose of disposables.  Drink from a glass whenever you can.  When you do drink from a disposable bottle, dispose of it in the recycling bin.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>11/19/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Hung up on all those extra wire hangers in your closet?  Recycle them!  Most dry cleaners will be happy to recycle your wire hangers, just drop them off with your clothes.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>11/20/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Suffocating in plastic dry cleaning bags?  If they are labeled #2 (HDPE) or #4 (LLDPE), you can recycle them (yes, there is such a thing as degradable poly).  Non-recyclable poly bags can be returned to your dry cleaner or taken to a <a href="http://www.plasticbagrecycling.org/01.0/" target="_blank">retail or recycling center</a>.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>11/21/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Don’t foul up your Thanksgiving!  Make a compassionate choice.  You can buy organic turkeys on the web and have them delivered overnight; <a href="http://www.localharvest.org/" target="_blank">LocalHarvest</a> can help you locate an organic turkey farm, or you can buy grocery store turkeys with the American Humane Society's <a href="http://www.americanhumane.org/site/PageServer?pagename=pa_farm_animals_ff_consumer_action" target="_blank">Free Farmed label</a>.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>11/22/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Do you give Green Thanks?  Take this <a href="http://planetgreen.discovery.com/games-quizzes/give-thanks-green-quiz/" target="_blank">Planet Green Thanksgiving quiz</a> to test your eco-smarts about how best to celebrate the holiday.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>11/23/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Think before you print.  Each piece of paper you don’t use saves .6 cents.  Resist the urge to print out just 15 pages a day and you can save $32 a year, and you’re well on your way to saving a tree too!]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>11/24/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[There is more carbon dioxide in the atmosphere now than there has been in the past <a href="http://www.thewe.cc/weplanet/news/air/co2_record_high_levels_in_the_atmosphere.htm" target="_blank">650,000 years</a>.  CO2 stays in the atmosphere and acts like a warm blanket that holds in the heat.  That’s why they call it the “greenhouse effect.”]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>11/25/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Thanksgiving, after all, is a word of action." - W.J.  Cameron]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>11/26/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Don’t throw out all that leftover Thanksgiving food!  Make a green and giving choice and donate it instead.  Many of the local food banks and shelters will be happy to help you unload your leftovers!  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>11/27/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Thinking about new outdoor holiday lights this year?  Save money, energy and the planet with light-emitting diodes, or LEDs.  They don’t cost more than incandescent lights and they use <a href="http://www.consumerreports.org/cro/home-garden/bed-bath/home-decoration/holiday-lights-incandescent-vs-led/overview/index.htm" target="_blank">90% less energy</a>.  Plus, they’re cool to the touch and extremely durable.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>11/28/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Going LED this year but don’t know what to do with your old incandescent Christmas lights?  <a href="http://www.holidayleds.com/holidayledscom_christmas_light_recycling_program" target=_new" target="_blank">HolidayLeds.com</a> will accept any retired strands for recycling.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>11/29/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Water is quickly becoming the most depleted natural resource of our time.  Not oil or gold, water.  In the next five years, the government projects that <a href="http://www.alternet.org/water/82378/" target="_blank">36 states will have a water shortage</a>.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>11/30/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Thanks to <a href="http://www.xerosltd.com/index.htm" target="_blank">Xeros</a>, waterless laundry is no longer an oxymoron.  An innovative new technology that replaces water with tiny reusable polymer beads, Xeros gets clothes clean with 90% less water.  Look for it to change the way the world does laundry.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>12/01/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Thinking about a new puppy for Christmas?  <a href="http://www.petfinder.com/index.html" target="_blank">Rescue a pet</a> from a local shelter.  It’s the greenest way to become a pet owner, and it’s usually tax deductible.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>12/02/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Green your greetings this year.  Save money, time and trees by sending e-cards instead of paper ones.  Most card companies offer e-cards, <a href="http://www.hallmark.com/webapp/wcs/stores/servlet/home%7c10001%7c10051%7c-1" target="_blank">Hallmark</a>, <a href="http://www.americangreetings.com/" target="_blank">American Greetings</a>, <a href="http://www.bluemountain.com/" target="_blank">Blue Mountain</a> etc.  You can even help a cause with <a href="http://www.care2.com/ecards/" target="_blank">Care2Make a Difference</a> or <a href="http://www.cardsforcauses.com/" target="_blank">Cards for Causes</a>.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>12/03/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[A greener choice for the kids on your list—'battery-free' gifts.  Batteries are a serious environmental hazard and about 40% of them are sold during the holidays.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>12/04/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[A green idea for decorating: use live greenery.  Thyme, rosemary and sage are evergreen, wonderfully fragrant herbs that can be re-used to season recipes after the holidays.  Basil, chamomile, lavender and mint all smell wonderful too.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>12/05/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[A delicious green decorating idea: put out bowls festooned with nuts, fruits, colorful squash, pomegranates, whole pineapples, etc.  It’s fun, practical and healthy too.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>12/06/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Looking for a hassle-free holiday eco-touch?  Sprinkle a few drops of a natural, essential oil like cedar wood, rose or sandalwood on pinecones or dried flowers.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>12/07/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[If crafts are your thing, <a href="http://www.wholeliving.com/article/eco-holiday-ideas" target="_blank">Martha Stewart</a> has a dozen eco-holiday ideas.  Each uses items most of us have on hand, and costs less than $10 to make.    ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>12/08/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Americans spend 2.7 billion a year on gift-wrap.  Much of it gets thrown away.  A fun solution:  wrap your gifts in the Sunday comics.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>12/09/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Try <a href="http://www.marthastewart.com/good-things/gift-tags" target="_blank">making your own gift tags this year</a>—it’s more personal and green!  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>12/10/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Looking for a green and giving gift idea this holiday season?  A <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Microcredit" target="_blank">micro-loan</a> through organizations like <a href="http://www.worldvisionmicro.org/?campaign=1209242&amp;cmp=KNC-1209242" target="_blank">World Vision</a> or <a href="http://www.kiva.org/" target="_blank">Kiva</a> can make a lasting difference.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>2/11/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Animal lovers on your list will love the gift of wildlife protection for newborn gray whales, polar bears or Yellowstone wolves.  For just $15 or $20, the <a href="http://www.savebiogems.org/giftsfromthewild/" target="_blank">Natural Resources Defense Council</a> will make a wildlife-saving gift in their name and send your personalized E-card.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>2/12/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Shipping holiday gifts?  Ground shipping is the greenest choice.  Sending packages by plane emits eight times more carbon dioxide than transporting by truck.  You can <a href="https://shop.usps.com/webapp/wcs/stores/servlet/CategoryDisplay?storeId=10052&amp;parent_category_rn=10000002&amp;categoryId=10000033&amp;top_category=10000002&amp;langId=-1&amp;catalogId=10001" target="_blank">order free eco-friendly Cradle-to-Cradle® packaging from USPS</a>.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>2/13/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Potted plants are thoughtful green gifts.  Not only do they keep on giving, they help improve indoor air quality.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>2/14/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Think outside the gift-box this year and try elegant, and green, Japanese <a href="http://furoshiki.com/techniques" target="_blank">furoshiki techniques</a> to wrap your gift in a gift of clothing or fabric.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>2/15/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[The great <a href="http://www.thedailygreen.com/green-homes/latest/christmas-trees-picking-greenest-options" target="_blank">green Tannenbaum debate</a>: real or artificial?  Experts are split.  If you want a real tree, the greenest choice is to buy or rent from a local tree farm.  If you take fake, be sure to buy American to reduce your impact.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>2/16/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Trying to minimize your travel footprint this holiday?  Resist the temptation to take those cute little complimentary bottles home and decline housekeeping.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>2/17/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Turkey doesn’t have to foul up your green holiday.  You can <a href="http://www.diamondorganics.com/" target="_blank">buy organic turkeys on the web</a> and have them delivered overnight; <a href="http://www.localharvest.org/" target="_blank">LocalHarvest</a> can help you locate an organic turkey farm, or you can buy grocery store turkeys with the American Humane Society's <a href="http://www.americanhumane.org/site/PageServer?pagename=pa_farm_animals_ff_consumer_action" target="_blank">Free Farmed label</a>.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>2/18/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Now is a great time to donate good quality clothing, books and unwanted gifts to charity shops like <a href="http://www.goodwill.org/" target="_blank">Goodwill</a>.  It is the greenest choice you can make and tax deductable too.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>2/19/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[E-gifts are the perfect, green solution for those last minute holiday gifts.  When you <a href="http://www.giftcard.com/" target="_blank">email a gift card</a> to business associates and loved ones, you eliminate paper waste (no need for cards or gift wrap!) and save valuable time, gasoline, and CO2!  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>2/20/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Make it a naked Christmas!  Save time, trees and money this year by not wrapping the gifts under the tree.  Americans throw away a million extra tons of garbage every week between Thanksgiving and New Year's.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>2/21/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[As we enter the holiday countdown, don’t let yourself get rundown or you will be <a href="http://www.cbsnews.com/stories/2009/12/08/earlyshow/health/main5938271.shtml" target="_blank">more susceptible to becoming ill</a>.  Make sure to get your zzzz’s and your D’s—vitamin D rich foods like tuna, cheese and milk help boost your immune system.  And don’t forget to wash your hands!  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>2/22/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Reduce, Reuse, Recycle…Re-gift!  If you’ve received a gift you can’t use, don’t throw it away or let it collect dust—the socially responsible choice is to re-gift it.  And, with <a href="http://www.fade2green.com/?p=60" target="_blank">67% of all people re-gifting</a>, it’s now a socially acceptable choice!   ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>2/23/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Looking for the perfect hostess gift?  A locally grown and/or organic wine wrapped in a beautiful eco-tote is a fun green choice.  For the cooking enthusiast:  an herb growing kit.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>2/24/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Set up for a sustainable Christmas morning.  Put out boxes for reusable wrapping paper (and ribbons and bows), gift boxes and gift cards that can be recycled, reusable packing materials (like foam and plastic air packs from electronic gifts).]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>2/25/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Christmas is a lot more than a date.  It’s a state of mind.  May your holiday spirit be evergreen!]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>2/26/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Today is the biggest day of the year for trash.  And a great day to learn how and where to <a href="http://www.ecocycle.org/askeco-cycle/20031226.cfm" target="_blank">recycle your holiday bags, boxes and lights</a>.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>2/27/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Recycling isn’t just for brown boxes; if you check with your local authority you will usually find that those left over gift boxes can usually be recycled too.  <a href="http://earth911.com/recycling/paper/wrapping-paper/facts-about-recycling-wrapping-paper/" target="_blank">Unfortunately most wrapping paper can’t be recycled</a>.  Shred it to stuff gift bags.]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>2/28/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.nrdc.org/cities/recycling/gelectronicsrecycling.asp" target="_blank">Eliminate e-waste</a>.  If you received new electronics for Christmas this year, give the used ones back to <a href="http://www.staples.com/" target="_blank">Staples</a>, <a href="http://www.officedepot.com/" target="_blank">Office Depot</a>, <a href="http://www.bestbuy.com/" target="_blank">Best Buy</a>,<a href="http://www.bestbuy.com/" target="_blank"> Apple</a>, <a href="http://www.dell.com/" target="_blank">Dell</a>, <a href="http://www.hp.com/#Product" target="_blank">Hewlett-Packard</a>, <a href="http://www.sony.com/" target="_blank">Sony</a>, <a href="http://www.gateway.com/" target="_blank">Gateway</a>, <a href="http://www.nokia.com/" target="_blank">Nokia</a>, <a href="http://www.motorola.com/" target="_blank">Motorola</a> and others or e-cycle locally at a recycling center.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>2/29/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Remember to “tree-cycle”!  Take a minute to <a href="http://earth911.com/" target="_blank">find a recycling center near you</a>.  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>2/30/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[Green suggestions for celebrating New Years:  celebrate in instead of out, use glass not plastic, use soy candles not synthetic, eat and drink foods made locally not far away, used shredded paper instead of buying petroleum-based confetti!  ]]></text>
  </tip>
  <tip>
    <day>2/31/2012</day>
    <text><![CDATA[You’re ready for New Year’s.  Are you ready for the day after?  Here are <a href="http://planetgreen.discovery.com/food-health/natural-hangover-cures.html" target="_blank">seven natural hangover remedies</a> to help your body clear out toxins and chemicals if you are “over-served”!]]></text>
  </tip>
</tips>
